# **Omar Vallejo**

vallejo.2015@gmail.com 706-575-5987

## **Profile**

### **Summary**

Proficiency in planning, staff coordination, collaborating with executives, researching IT solutions and implementing them into systems and infrastructure are my strengths. Offering three-plus years of customer service and technical competence. Constantly dedicated to learning new technology and always striving for the best.

## Skills

### **Technical Skills**

- Java HTML Python Visual Basic SQL
- Troubleshooting Technical Issues
- OS Installations & Upgrades Mac OS Windows OS Ubuntu OS
- Microsoft Office Suite
- Google Suite

#### **Overall Skills**

- Supervisor Experience
- Bilingual English and Spanish
- Great Team Worker
- Project Leader
- Customer Satisfaction Determined

# **Work Experience**

## **Columbus State University – Lead PC Repair Technician**

04/2017 - Current

Team Leadership: Supervisor of 4 employees including in charge of training new employees, scheduling, professional development & discipline. Full network support for all dorms. Strategic planning, inventory management, work lab system optimizations and researching IT solutions providing recommendations for improvement to the university's Technology Department. Hardware and software repair/upgrades and support for students, faculty, and staff.

## **Columbus State University – Cyber Security Department Internship**

1/2018 - 4/2018

Execute tasks such as Audits, Cyber Security Awareness presentations, web page editing, critical document disposal and monitoring user access to the university's network.

## Marco's Pizza-Delivery Driver

01/2017 - 3/2018

Ensured customer satisfaction through excellent communication and time management.

## **Education**

# **Columbus State University – Bachelor of Science in Information Technology** 8/2015 – Current

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science, Information Technology. Graduation date of May 2019.